Guide to the Eunice Johnson Collection on Timothy Richard)
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Eunice Johnson Papers, 1867-2002; Series III
  - Source Guides and Bibliographies, 1867-1997
    - Research Guide to the Wan-Kuo Kung-Pao ("The Globe Magazine") 1874-1883, Compiled by Adrian A. Bennett, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Select Bibliography and Research Guide from Education and Modernization: The Chinese Experience, by Ruth Hayhoe, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - A Selected Bibliography of Missionary Literature, Compiled by J. Lovell Murray (photocopies of selected pages), 1920 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Serials: Missions (Allenson), 08 Mar 1993 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Twentieth Century Evangelicalism: A Guide to the Sources (photocopies of selected pages), by Edith L. Blumhofer and Joel A. Carpenter, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - UMI-China A Selected Collection of Doctoral Dissertations and Masters Theses (1980-1986), 1980-1987 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - US Congress: Shanxi-Boxer Rebellion-Missionary, 1870-1910 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - University of Hong Kong - Upcoming Publications, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - W.A.P. Martin: Pioneer of Progress in China - Bibliography, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Collected Bibliographies and Source Guides from various locations (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Collected Bibliographies and Source Guides from various locations (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Collected Bibliographies and Source Guides from various locations (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Collected Bibliographies and Source Guides from various locations (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Memorabilia and Photographs from the Shanxi University Centennial Celebration (1902-2002)
    - Shanxi University Centennial Celebration Guides, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Pamphlet for Overseas Students Studying at Shanxi University, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Shanxi University Centennial Memorabilia, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Shanxi University Centennial - Photographs of and relating to the celebration, 2002 May (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Shanxi University Centennial - Photographs of and relating to the celebration, 2002 May (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Photographs from Moir Duncan's grave site and the temple where he died, 2002 May (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Shanxi University visor, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Shanxi University The Centennial Anniversary (Video CD), 2002 (Box 19, Folder 13)